Guide to the Harwood Family Papers, 1722-1962
Department of Special Collections
- 145. 1881, Sept. 23,ptd. ticket Obsequies of the Late President James A. Garfield in Rotunda of Capitol.
- 146. 1881, Oct. 22,J. C. Kelton to Geo. S. Wilson LS and ANS re: camp Huachuca, Arizona Terr. - with typescript copy and typescript copy of Nov. 12 enclosure.
- 147. 1884, June 30,ALS Geo [S. Wilson] to [Sarah?]
- 148. 1884, July 24,ptd. concert program complimentary t Miss Margaret Spencer Wilson.
- 149. 1884, Sept. 3,General Orders announcing death of Rear Admiral Harwood - ptd.
- 150. 1885, Feb. 6,Ptd. Senate Report No. 1174 pension for Margaret B. Harwood (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 151. 1886, Mar. 2,ptd. HR Report No. 817, Margaret B. Harwood Pension
- 152. 1886,W. E. Doyle, History of the Seventeenth Indian - original edition - 1865.
- 153. 1887, June 27,G. A. R. LaFayette Post No. 140, Dept of NY, ptd. announcement - G.S. Wilson a recruit.
- 154. 1888, Mar. 2,W. O. Gresham to Geo. S. Wilson ALS
- 155. 1889, Feb. 10,Francis F. Cleveland to Bessie Harwood ALS
- 156. 1890, Aug. 13,ALS Wm. James to Dear Katherine.
- 157. 1891, Nov. 4,Geo. S. Wilson Wilder's Brigade of Mounted Infantry in Tullahama: Chicamauga Campaigns ptd. paper for Kansas Commandery of the M.O.L.L.U.S.
- 158. 1891, Nov. 22,ALS Wm. M. [Wherry]? to [Geo. S.] Wilson re: forming an Infantry Association.
- 159. 1891,Dec. Geo. S. Wilson, ptd. art. The Enlisted Men of the United States Army, Journal of the U: S. Cavalry Assoc., extra from an address re: Wm. H. Jones, d.k.t.
- 160. 1892, Jan. 15,R. W. Gilder to Miss E. F. Harwood AL (Box 1, Folder 20)
- 161. 1892, Jan. 15,Edwin Booth to Miss E. F. Harwood AL
- 162. 1892, May 13,J. C. Bechinridge to Geo. S. Wilson AL
- 163. 1892, June 10,ALS John G. Bourke to Geo. S. Wilson
- 164. 1893, Mar. 23,James H. Wilson to Geo S.Wilson, copy, s. C. W. Abbot, Jr.
- 165. 1893, Mar. 29,J. T. Wilder to Sec. of War, copy s. C. W. Abbot, Jr.
- 166. 1893, April 6,Geo. L. Shoup to Geo. S. Wilson copy
- 167. 1893, April 9,J. G. Fisher to Sec. of War copy
- 168. 1893, April 19,U.S. Infantry Society ptd. brochure G. S. Wilson, founder, Corresp. Sec.
- 169. 1893, May 3,E. F. Townsend to Adj. Gen. U.S. Army copy
- 170. 1893, May 4,Harry C. Egbert to Sec. of War, copy
- 171. 1893, May 31,A. O. Miller to Sec. of War, copy
- 172. 1893, June 12,Thos. T. Dill to Daniel S. Lamont copy re: GSW applic. (Box 1, Folder 21)
- 173. 1893, June 17,DS Geo. S. Wilson Summary of Military History of Capt. Geo. Spencer Wilson.
- 174. 1893, June 19,ALS Geo. S. Wilson to Judge [], application for appt. in A. G. Dept. as Major.
- 175. 1893, June,LS Geo. S. Wilson to Adj. Gen. U.S.A. application. list of recommendations.
- 176. 1893, Nov. 6,W. O. Gresham to Geo.S.Wilson-telegram
- 177. 1893, Nov. 6,Appointment of Wilson as Asst. to Adj. s. Daniel S. Lamont.
- 178. 1893, Nov. 6,Henry C. Corbin to Geo. S. Wilson -tel
- 179. 1893, Nov. 7,Hugh G. Brown to Geo. S. Wilson -tel.
- 180. 1893, Nov. 7,J.C. Burnett to Geo. S. Wilson -tel.
- 181. 1893, Nov. 7,Fred A. Smith to Geo. S. Wilson -tel.
- 182. 1893, Nov. 7,Theodore Masher to Geo. S. Wilson -tel
- 183. 1893, Nov. 7,G. F. Cooke to Geo. S. Wilson -tel.
- 184. 1893, Nov. 7,C.E. Tayman to Geo. S. Wilson -tel.
- 185. 1893, Nov. 7,W. H. Gordon to Geo. S. Wilson -tel.
- 186. 1893, Nov. 7,J. M. Nuckles to Geo. S. Wilson -tel.
- 187. 1893, Nov. 7,ALS [Wothirspooh] to GSWilson
- 188. 1893, Nov. 8,ALS U. L. Pitcher to G. S. Wilson
- 189. 1893, Dec. 12,Adj. Gen. Off. to G. S. Wilson - copy tel. s. J.C. Gilmore. apptmt as AAG and Maj.
- 190. [1893],O. B. Willcox - cert. of service of G. S. Wilson copy
- 191. 1894, Jan. 10,J. T. Wilder to G. S. Wilson ALS (Box 1, Folder 22)
- 192. 1894, Jan. 22,W. Q. Gresham to G. S. Wilson LS
- 193. 1895, Aug. 7,U.S. Inf. Soc. ptd circ. letter -re: essay prize and medal
- 194. 1896,G. S. Wilson - The Army; Its Employment During Time of Peace, and the Necessity for its Increase. Monographs of the U.S. Inf. Soc. - No. 1 Prize essay for 1896, (3 copies)
- 195. 1896, Mar. 9,ALS Nat P. Phister to G. S. Wilson - prize money for essay.
- 196. Mar. 30,Theodore Roosevelt to G. S. Wilson LS
- 197. 1896, May 3,Two New York Sun clips re: Wilson's essay. (Box 1, Folder 23)
- 198. 1896, May 14,ALS A. [McClune] to G. S. Wilson
- 199. 1896, July 7,Oswald Garrison Villard to GSW ALS
- 200. 1896, July 14,[GSW] to Maj. Gen. Curdg - the army carbon
- 201. 1896, July 27,Oswald Garrison Villard to GSW ALS
- 202. 1896, Oct. 17,Portland, Oregon. Commercial Club ptd. program - 3rd annual dinner.
- 203. 1896, Oct. 17,GSW typed copy of his toast at Commercial Club Dinner
- 204. [1896, Nov. 21],Weekly Outlook, [Davenport, Iowa] clip
- 205. 1896, Dec. 4,[GSW] to Andrew H. Russell I copy, typescript
- 206. [1897]clip re: Late Maj. Wilson (Box 2, Folder 24)
- 207. 1897, Jan. 13,ALS Wm. M. Wherry to Mrs. Wilson
- 208. 1897, Jan. 13,J. M. Marshall to R. Douglass Burnet tel. re: taking body of GSW to San Francisco, Cal.
- 209. 1897, Jan. 13,Portland Oregonian - clip obit. GSW, 2 copies
- 210. 1897, Jan. 15,San Francisco Bulletin, clip obit. GSW
- 211. 1897, Jan. 18,War Dept. AGO ptd. announcement of death of GSW
- 212. 1897, Jan. 18,ALS A.A. DeLaffre to Mrs. Wilson
- 213. [1897, Jan. 23]The Army and Navy Journal. clip obit. of GSW, 2 copies
- 214. 1897, Feb.M.O.L.L.U.S. ptd. memorial to GSW
- 215. 1900, Jan. 28,[Emil] Fischer ANS note and clip in German, Nobel Prize Winner. (Box 2, Folder 25)
- 216. 1902, May 23,Hamlin School, San Francisco, ptd. Commencement invitation and program - Margaret Spencer Wilson.
- 217. 1903, April 21,R. W. Gilder to Sally ALS
- 218. 1905, Dec. 11,W. D. Howells to William James ALS and cvr. re: Confessions of an Ambitious Mother.
- 219. 1908-09,)Panama Railroad Co. Pass to Jeromel Fee s. Geo. W. Goethals, D. J. Fee
- 220. 1910, Dec. 20,Booker T. Washington to Huntington ALS
- 221. 1912, May 15,Geo. W. Cable to Dr. Rice ALS
- 222. 1913, Oct. 18,R. W. Gilder, two stanzas of a poem, (undated)AS, and printed copy of The Old House with signed notes of Gilder.
- 223. 1920, Sept. 2,J. P. Tumulty to Wilson Franklin Harwood LS
- 224. 1922, March 6,Anna Pavlova to Geo. P. McNear LS
- 225. 1922, Sept. 12,Warring G. Harding to Sarah W. Harwood LS with cvr.
- 226. 1924, July 1,W. Lee Lewis to David Star Jordan carbon - Science and Sciosophy
- 227. 1924, July 14,David Star Jordan to W. Lee Lewis TLS reply to #226, re; Lewisite, wars.
- 228. 1925, Nov. 18,Franklin D. Roosevelt to Sarah W. Harwood LS and cvr.
- 229. 1928, Aug. 11,Ray Lyman Wilbur to Mrs. F. B. Harwood -declines an invitation to speak. (Box 2, Folder 26)
- 230. 1928, Nov. 15,Herbert Hoover to Sally Franklin Harwood LS
- 231. 1936, Sept 18,Ray Lyman Wilbur to Winifred Lee Lewis TLS
- 232. 1937, March 26,Oswald Garrison Villard to Wilson F. Harwood LS
- 233. 1938, June 14,Vilhjalmur Stefansson to W. Lee Lewis TLS
- 234. 1938, June 30,W. Lee Lewis to Vilhjalmur Steffansson carbon
- 235. 1939, July 23,Chicago Sunday Herold clip - W. Lee Lewis re: use of war gas.
- 236. 1939, Oct. 12,Vilhjalmur Stefansson to W. Lee Lewis TLS re: salt
- 237. 1939, Nov. 13, Colonel Lewis on Lewisite ptd. responses from radio broadcast #Adventures in Science.
- 238. 1940, March 27,Carl Sandburg to Mrs. F. B. Harwood TNS
- 239. 1940, April 29,Carl Sandburg to Mrs. F. B. Harwood RLS re: a Lincoln letter
- 240. 1940, May 13,Carl Sandburg to Mr. Harwood TLS re: thanks for sending Lincoln and Bates letters
- 241. 1940, May 20,Max Farrand to Wilson F. Harwood and note on the Franklin Papers
- 242. 1940, Sept. 26,Carl Sandburg to Mr. Harwood TLS re: Lincoln letters.
- 243. 1940, Dec. 9,Herbert Hoover to W. Lee Lewis TLS re: Stanford Refunders Club to raise money
- 244. 1940, Dec. 16,Ray Lyman Wilbur to W. Lee Lewis TLS
- 245. [ca. 1940]Beniamino [Bufano] to Bob ALS - Helen Gahagan, state NYA project, Aubrey
- 246. 1941, Jan. 2,Herbert Hoover to W. Lee Lewis TLS (Box 2, Folder 27)
- 247. 1941, May 12,Clarence Street to Mr. Scott ALS Federal Union- U.S. and six Brit. Democracies
- 248. 1941, July 14,Harry E. Fosdick to Mrs. Margaret B. Harwood TNS pacifist and non-interventionist
- 249. 1941, July 15,Herbert Hoover to Mrs. F. B. Harwood TNS
- 250. 1941, July 18,Robert M. Hutchins to Mrs. F. B. Harwood TNS
- 251. 1941, Nov. 27,Nelson A. Rockefeller to Wilson F. Harwood TLS re: a position for F. B. Harwood - Inter-American Affairs.
- 252. 1942, March 17,Pearl S. Buck to Mrs. F. B. Harwood TNS
- 253. 1946, Oct. 17,Henry A. Wallace to Mrs. F. B. Harwood TLS
- 254. 1947, July 21,William Rose Benét to Mrs. Harwood ALS
- 255. 1949, Mar. 31,Winston Churchill - ticket to Boston Address
- 256. 1950, May 16,Harry Truman to Dael Wolfle TLS re: recommends for membership on Nat. Science Board.
- 257. 1953, Nov. 11,Adlai E. Stevenson to Mrs. Harwood TNS
- 258. 1953, Dec. 1,Pres. and Mrs. Eisenhower ptd. invitation to White House reception and gate pass in cvr.
- 259. 1956, Jan. 21,Detlev W. Bronk, to Wilson F. Harwood TLS
- 260. 1962, Mar. 1,Sargent Shriver to Mrs. Lee Harwood TNS
- 1898 - 1906F. B. Harwood Orders [FRANKLIN Bache Harwood 1876 -] (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 1. 1898, May 18,Navy Dept. Bur. of Navigation to Franklin B. Harwood stp. A.S. Crowninshield copy present self for line officer exams. Dkt May 23, 1898 TNS H.L.H.[ouison]; May 26, 1898 ANS Allan D. Brown
  - 2. 1898, June 2,Navy Dept. Bur. of Nav. to F. B. Harwood s. [F.W.] Dickins: apptmt as ensign
  - 3. 1898, June 7,Navy Dept. to F. B. Harwood s. Chas. H.Allen (Acting Sec.): orders to report to Scipio Dkt: June 9, 1898 TNS F. M. Bunce, ANS Jno P. Merrell
  - 4. 1898, July 6,John D. Long to Franklin B. Harwood L
  - 5. 1898, Sept 18,J.C. Watson to F.B. Harwood TDS orders to temp. duty on Vulcan. Dkt: Sept, 18 ANS Jno P. Merrell, Sept, [17]? ANS Ira Harris, Sept. 20, ANS Jno P. Merrell.
  - 6. 1899, March 29,Treas. Dept. Aud. for Navy Dept. to F.B. Harwood s. F.H. Morris
  - 7. 1899, Aug. 1,Treas. Dept. to F. B. Harwood TDS s. C.F. Shoemaker: apptmt as cadet, Revenue Cutter Service
  - 8. 1899, Aug. 7,Treas. Dept. to F. B. Harwood s. Asst Sec. O.L. Spaulding TDS report to Chase Dkt. 8/14 ANS E. C. Ch[], ANS O.C. Hamlet
  - 9. 1899, Aug. 7,Lyman Gage to Franklin B. Harwood LS
  - 10. 1900, Oct. 19,Rev. Cutter Service Report of Averages Cadet Exam
  - 11. 1901, Aprl 23,Treas. Dept. To F.B. Harwood s.Asst. Sec. O.L. Spaulding report to Onondaga 4/30 ANS David [F.] Hall Dkt. 5/1 ANS W.C. DeHart
  - 12. 1901, Aug. 6,C.F. Shoemaker to F.B. Harwood, TDS apptmt as 3rd lieut.
  - 13. 190., Sept. 13,C.F. Shoemaker to F. B. Harwood, TNS and ANS 9/14 W.C.DeHart
  - 14. 1901, Sept 26,Treas. Dept. to F. B. Harwood s. O.L. Spaulding, Act. Sec. 9/27 ANS W.C. DeHart; temp. leave.
  - 15. 1902, April 17,Treas Dept to FBH s. Act. Sec - O.I Spaulding, 4/18 ANS W.C. DeHart, 4/25 ANS W.D. Roath: report to Hamilton
  - 16. 1902, April 18,H.A. Taylor (Asst. Sec) to FBH-telre: leave; with AN [Harwood] on verso
  - 17. 1902, May 15,Treas, Dept To FBH
  - 18. 1902, May 24,C.F. Shoemaker to FBH TNS
  - 19. 1902, June 2,Treas. Dept. to FBH
  - 20. 1902, July 12,C.F. Shoemaker to FBH TNS
  - 21. 1902, July 29,Treas. Dept. Act. Sec. (O.L. Spaulding to FBH TNS 7/31 ANS W.D.Roath
  - 22. 1902, Aug. 18,Treas. Dept. to FBH s. H.A. Taylor
  - 23. 1902, Oct. 17,Treas. Dept. O.L. Spaulding - Act. Sec. - to FBH DS; ANS 10/19 W.D.Roath: assigned to Forward Dkt: 10/31 ANS F.S. Van BosKerk, Jr.
  - 24. 1902, Oct. 23,Treas. Dept. ptd. Circ. 1tr. No. 3 to Officers of Revenue Cutter Service
  - 25. 1902, Oct. 29,W.D. Roath to FBH TNS
  - 26. 1902, Dec. 3,Treas. Dept. to FBH s. O.L.Spaulding report to Boutwell for temp. duty; 12/05 ANS W.S. Howland, Dkt. 12/8 ANS J. A. Sla[?]
  - 27. 1903, Jan. 6.Treas. Dept to F. B. Harwood s. O.L. Spaulding temp. duty Onondaga Dkt. 1/11 ANS J.A. Sla[?], 1/22 ANS Worth[G.] Ross
  - 28. 1903, Jan. 8,Treas. Dept. to F.B. Harwood s. O.L. Spaulding
  - 29. 1903, Jan. 12,O.L. Spaulding to F.B. Harwood tel.
  - 30. 1903, Jan. 15,[H].A. or B. A. Tayler to F.B. Harwood tel.
  - 31. 1903, Jan. 19,H. A. Tayler to F.B. Harwood tel.
  - 32. 1903, Feb. 7,C.F. Shoemaker to F. B. Harwood TNS
  - 33. 1903, Feb. 24,Treas. Dept. to F.B. Harwood s.O.L. Spaulding report to Bear 2/25 ANS Worth G. Ross, 3/23 ANS F. Tuttle
  - 34. 1903, May 28,C.F. Shoemaker to F. B. Harwood TNS
  - 35. 1904, Mar. 12,J.F.Wild to F.B. Harwood TNS to report for exam for 2nd 1t.
  - 36. 1904, Mar. 15,F. Tuttle to F.B. Harwood carbon signed
  - 37. 1904, April 30,C. F. Shoemaker to F.B. Harwood TLS promotion to 2nd 1t., exam marks
  - 38. 1904, May 4,C.F. Shoemaker to F.B. Harwood TLS
  - 39. 1904, July 12,Treas. Dept to F.B. Harwood s.R.B. Armstrong report to Manning 7/21 ANS F. Tuttle; ANS O.D. [Wyrick] on verso
  - 40. 1904, Dec. 8,Treas. Dept. to F.B. Harwood s. R.B. Armstrong
  - 41. 1904, Dec. 20,C.F. Shoemaker to F.B. Harwood TNS transmits 2nd 1t. cmmn.
  - 42. 1905, Oct. 3,Worth G. Ross to F.B. Harwood TNS
  - 43. 1905, Nov. 4,HA Tayler to F.B. Harwood tel. ANS F. tuttle
  - 44. 1905, Nov. 5,F. Tuttle to F. B. Harwood TNS temp. duty McCulloch ANS J.C. Cantwell
  - 45. 1905, Nov. 9,Treas. Dept. to F.B. Harwood s. H.A. Tayler
  - 46. 1905, Dec. 22,Treas. Dept to F.B. Harwood s. H.A. Tayler
  - 47. 1906, Jan. 4,Worth G. Ross to F. B. Harwood TNS
  - 48. 1906, June 8,Treas. Dept. to F.B. Harwood s. H.A. Tayler
- Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 1. Poem by John Edmund Harwood - W. Whitesides
  - 2. Augustin Pyrame A[ustin] P[yramus] de Candolle to Bache -in French ALS
  - 3. Von Humbolt to [] -in French? ALS
  - 4. Theodore Parker to [] ALS
  - 5. Aug. 30,James C. Dobbin to Edward ALS
  - 6. James C. Dobbin to Edward ALS
  - 7. Nov. 4,H. Guy C. Corbin to Geo. S. Wilson ALS
  - 8. L. Murel(?) to Harwood ALS
  - 9. Christmas day, Frank Taylor to Harwood ALS
  - 10. Cyrus Wakeham to [] ALS
  - 11. Charles Lion to [] ALS
  - 12. Commander Casy to Harwood in 3rd person
  - 13, [Geo. S. Wilson] Adf. of speech or paper re: Kansas Commandery of the Loyal Legion
  - 14. The Ladder of St. Augustine, poem by Henry W. Longfellow ADS
  - 15. (James Brander) Brandes Matthews to Dear Madame LS
  - 16. envelope of recipes of my Grandmother's [?] d. 1901
- Engravings, etc. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 1. The High Priest of Tahiti Ceding the District of Matavai to Capt. Wilson, for the Missionaries; Fisher, Son and Co. London 1829.Engr. by H. Robinson, Painted by R. Smirke A. R. A.
  - 2. Andw. A. Harwood photo with signature
  - 3. Benjamin Franklin Engraved by T. B. Welch from the portrait by Martin in possession of the Amer, Phil. Soc. Facs. Signature James H. Lamb Co.
  - 4. Basso rilievo del Muses di Siracusa engraving
  - 5. Adml. Van Troup engraving J. Chapman [sculp.] Published as the Act directs April 2, 1798.
  - 6. Lt. Gen. Sir Rufane Shawe Donkin, K.C.B. and G.C. H w facs. sign. Engv. W. Holl, Painter - H. Mayer Fisher, Son and Co. London 1831.
  - 7. Maj. Gen. Wm. Moultrie engraving (proof)? some pencil lines
  - 8. Horatio, Viscount Nelson, Engagement off Cape St. Vincent 1797. Painter - Hoppner, Engvr. J. Rogers, J.&F. Tallis, London and Glasgow
  - 9. John Jervis, Earl of St. Vincent, OB. 1823.Engvr. H. Robinson from the original of Hoppner, in His Majesty's Collection. London, Published Aug. 1, 1830by Harding and Lepard. Pall Mall East.
  - 10. Sir Thomas Munro Bart. K.C.B. Painted by M. A. Shee P.R.A., Engvr. H. Meyer facs. sig. Fisher, Son and Co. London 1830
  - 11. General Oglethorpe - engraving, Ravenet sculp.
  - 12. Maj. Gen. Sullivan - engraving, facs. sig. (proof?) some pencil work.
  - 13. Capt. James Newman Newman, R.N. Engraved by E. Scriven, Historical Engraver to the Prince Regent & the princess of Wales. From a painting by A.J. Olive A.R.A., Published Oct. 30th, 1813by Joyce Gold, Nava Chronicle Office 103 Shoe Lane London
  - 14. Nelson. Engrvd by E. Scriven from a miniature for which Lord Nelson Set to Mr. Bowyer. Pub. 9th Dec. 1805by R. Bowyer PallMall
  - 15. Capt. Sir John Ross R.N. Knt. K.S. etc.etc. facs. sig. Drawn by Thomas H. Shepherd. Engrvd by W.Watkins London: Geo. Virtue
  - 16. Sr. Edward Hawke Knight of the Most Honble Order of the Bath, and Rear Admiral of the White Squadron of His Majesty's Fleet. For the Lond: Mag. Printed for R. Baldwin in Pater Noster Row.
  - 17. Charles II. engraving
  - 18. Lord Viscount Howe, Argus sculp. European Mag. Publ Nov. 1, 1782by I. Fielding, Pater-Noster Row, I. Sewell, Cornhill, & I. Debrett. Piccadilly.
  - 19. The Rt. Honble Alexander Hood, Viscount Bridport, K.B. facs. signature. Painted by L.F. Abbott, Engrvd by S. Freeman. Fisher, Son & Co., London, 1832.
  - 20. Capt. James Cook. F.R.S. The Most Striking Likeness of the Late --- engraving. He was Born at Marton in the North Riding of Yorkshire Nov. 3, 1728,and unfortunately Killed by the Savages of the Island OWhyhee, Feb. 14, 1779.
  - 21. William-Carr Beresford, D.C.L. Viscount Beresford. facs. sig. Sir Wm. Beechey, R.A., P.W.Tomkins, Esq. Fisher, Son & Co. London 1830
  - 22. John Jervis, Earl of St. Vincent. K.B. facs. sig. I(or J) Keenan J. Cochran, Fisher, son & Co. London 1929
  - 23. Sir Edward Cadrington, G.C.B. etc. etc. Vice Admira of the White Squadron of His Majesty's Fleet. facs. sig. Painted by Sir Thos. Lawrence P.R.A. Engrvd by J. Cochran Fisher, Son & Co. London 1830
  - 24. The Late lieut. Gen. Alexander MacKenzie Frazer engraving
  - 25. Louis Philippe I. King of the French. Born in Paris Oct. 6, 1773.engraving F. Gerard, Pinxt. Delivered Grates to the Purchasers of the Bell's New Weekly Messenger Jan. 14th & 15th 1837
  - 26. Sr. Geo. Rooke engraving Benoist sculp.
  - 27. James Biddle Esqr. Of the United States Navy. Wood del. Gunbrede sculpt. Engraved for the Analectic Mag. Publ. by M. Thomas.
  - 28. Sir Thomas Picton. G.C.B. facs. sig. Painted by Sir Wm. Beechey, R.A. Engraved by P.W. Tomkins Fisher, Son & Co. London, 1830
  - 29. Major Gen. David Stewart of Garth. J. Watson Gordon J.B. Shaw. Publ. by Blackie & Son, Glasgow
  - 30. Nelson. facs. sig. W. Read sculpt. London Publ. by Richard Bentley 1836
  - 31. Earl Howe engraving
  - 32. Admiral Vernon Benoist sculp.
  - 33. Edward, Duke of Kent & Strathearn, K.G. - K.T. - K. St. P. etc. facs. sig. Painted by Sir Wm. Beeche R.A. Engraved by E.Scriven Fisher, Son & Co. London 1830pencilled notes, biog. & descriptive
  - 34. Lord Nelson-engraving
  - 35. Sir John Franklin Capt. R.N. facs. sig. Derby Thomson Fisher, Son & Co. London 1830
  - 36. Gen. Abercrombie European Mag. Ridley sc., Pub. by J. Sewell 32 Cornhill July 1, 1801.
  - 37. Lord Cochrane R. Cooper sc.
  - 38. The Rt. Honble Lord Collingwood. Engrvd by Ridley by permission of Messrs. Clay & Scriven European Mag. Publ. by J. Asperne at the Bible, Crown & Constitution, Cornhill, June 1, 1810.
  - 39. Henry William Paget. Marquess of Anglessey. K.G. etc., Lord Lieut.-Gen. and Gen-Governor of Ireland, etc. facs. sig. Painted by Sir Thos. Lawrence,Engraved by S. Freeman Fisher, Son & Co. London 1831.
  - 40. The Rt. Hon. Lieut. Gen. Sir Geo. Murray.G.C.B. F.R.S. etc. facs. sig. Painted by Sir Thos. Lawrence P.R.A. Engraved by H. Meyer,Fisher, Son & Co. London 1831
  - 41. Il Fonte Crane la Pisma?engraving proof
  - 42. Il Fonte Aretresa G.P.? engraving proof
  - 43. Benjamin Franklin photo of oil by Duplessis
  - 44. John Hancock facs. sig. Engraved by I.B. Forrest, Painted by J. Herring from the orig. by J.S.Copley in Faneuil Hall.
    signed out - no location listed
  - 45. John Caldwell Calhoun facs. sig. Engraved by T.B. Welch from a Drawing by J.B. Longacre
  - 46. [Duke of Cumberland, Bro. of Geo. III] engraving
  - 47. Charles Howard, Earl of Nottingham OB 1624 Engrvd by J. Jenkins From the orig. in the collection of the Rt. Honble the Earl of Verulam. Publ. by Harding, Triphock & Lepard, Finsburg Square London April 1, 1825.
  - 48. William the Fourth engraving?proof
  - 49. Lieut. Gen. Sir Ralph Abercromby K.B. facs. sig. Painted by J. Hoppner, R.A. Engrvd by H.D.Cook Fisher, Son & Co. London 1831
  - 50. Cuthbert Collingwood. Baron Collingwood facs. sig. Painted by F. Howard Esqr. Engrved by W. Finden Fisher, Son & Co. London 1832.
  - 51. Capt. Jos. Huddart. F.R.S. Painted by John Hoppner, Esqr, RA Engrvd by James Stow From a picture in the Possession of Chas. Turner Esqr. (4×4×3×4ft.). London; publ. 2nd Nov. 1801by Lauris & Whittle, Fleet Street & Charles Turner of Limehouse Ptd. by J. Collins []
  - 52. James Abram Garfield Pres. of the United States 1881,John A. Lowell Bank Note Co. Boston USA Copyright 1910
  - 53. Amerigo Vespucci, pencil drawing for (or from) an etching [Teschiero] L'originale existe [UNK] [UNK] Reale di Firenze
  - 54. _____ photo Civil War officer (navy)
  - 55. _____ 3 mounted photos Civil War period (navy offr. cntr.)
  - 56. _____ photo pre-Civil War officer
  - 57. _____ photo pre-Civil War officer -army (Brady photo)
  - 58. [F.B. Harwood?] photo pre-Civil War officer -navy (ensign?)
  - 59. Sophia Dallas Bache photo
  - 60. [Burke?] photo -navy
  - 61. _____ photo of painting of woman
  - 62. H. P. Babcock photo -navy Asst. Surg.
  - 63. _____ photo -mounted man and woman
  - 64. [Stringham -lft.; Van Brunt -rt.?] photo -mounted
  - 65. [Stringham?] photo -mounted
  - 66. [? -top; Winfield Scott -bottom?] photo -mounted
  - 67. _____ photo -mounted -navy
  - 68. _____ photo -mounted -navy
  - 69. _____ photo -mounted - woman
  - 70. W. Gould Turkish Bath Smyrna 1954Dozing Crisis water color photo [of Gould?]
  - 71. _____ photo -navy
  - 72. Monument erected at the Navy Yard Washington. Engrvd. for the Analectic Magazine and Naval Chronicle. Published by M. Thomas
  - 73. David Porter Esqr. of the United States Navy. Wood. Pinxt. Edwin sc. Engraved for Analectic Magazine Published by M. Thomas.
  - 74. Commodore Barney Wood. Pinxt. Childs & Gunber sc.
  - 75. Oliver H. Perry Esq. of the United States Navy Waldo pinxit. Edwin sc. Engraved for Analectic Magazine - Entered according to Act of Congress 18__.
  - 76. Lewis Washington Esqr. of the United States Navy Jarvis Pinxt. Gambrede Sculpt. Engraved for the Analectic Mag. - Published by M. Thomas. Copy Right Secured According to Act of Congress Oct. 2, 1815.Printed by Rogers & F._____
  - 77. James Lawrence Esqr. Late of the United States Navy Stuart pinxt. Rollinson sct. Engraved for the Analectic Mag.
  - 78. [Martha Washington] Engraved by J.B. Longacre from an original miniature by Robertson -in possession of G.W.P. Custis.
    signed out - no location given
  - 79. Young woman Engraved by J. Cheney & J.G. Kellogg
  - 80. James Madison Aged 82 facs. sig. Engraved by T.B. Welch from a drawing by J.B. Longacre taken from life at Montpelier Va. July, 1833.
  - 81. _____ Painted by J.W. Jarvis Engraved by T. Woolnoth.
  - 82. Margaret Wilson and Marian Huntington (d. of C.P.) ca. 1905.Chutes San Francisco Souvenie Tin Type.
    missing
  - 83. [U.S.Grant] Daguerreotype by M.B. Brady Engraved by R. Whitechurch.
  - 84. Nathaniel Parker Willis photo & typed biog. note
  - 85. _____ photo
  - 86. George Polhill engraved portrait & ptd. calling card.
  - 87. [A.A. Harwood] photo
  - 88. Franklin D. Roosevelt engraved portrait
  - 89. [James Monroe?] Engrvd by A.B. Durand from the painting by J. Vanderlyn in the City Hall New York
  - 90. Col. Wm. Duane engraved portrait
  - 91. [Alexander Hamilton] Engrvd by E. Prud'homme from the original miniature by Arch. Robertson.
- Autographs, etc. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - 1. John A. Barney autograph with engraved portrait
  - 2. Benjamin Franklin engraved portrait on verso of #1
  - 3. Charles Cotesworth Pinkney, Autograph and engraved portrait
  - 4. H[enry] Knox autograph and engraved portrait
  - 5. Thomas Pinckney autograph and engraved portrait and typed biog. sketch
  - 6. Thomas Pinkney verso Timothy Pickering 2 autographs engraved portrait & typed biog. sketch.